elitestore.net 2010-12-30

# Privacy Notice : Fastest Online Store

Effective **01/01/2005**

**     Our Commitment To Privacy:**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this policy explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available from a link positioned on the homepage of this internet website. 

**  The Information That Is Collected:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

**The Way The Information Is Utilized:**

The information you provide about yourself when placing an order is needed to complete your order. The information to used to verify your identity. This information is used to process your credit card information. We use the information to process and ship your order. We use the information to track your order when needed. We do not share this information with outside parties except to delivery service companies, credit card processing agencies and banks, and other companies as required or allowed by law. The information may be shared with firms including accountants, lawyers, government agencies and other parties as may be required or allowed by law. The information may be used by leased personnel or seasonal staffing companies and their personnel to process your order. The information may be used by contracted warehouses and freight lines necessary to fulfill your order in a timely manner.

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent as described above.

We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose except to provide you with information we feel would be of interest to you and are shared with other parties, including internet companies which are necessary to use in order to transmit e-mails, to send you this information.

We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers and others. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways related or unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such uses. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security:**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Information:**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by saving your email confirmations and/or writing to us. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before making corrections. 

**Privacy Notice Revisions:**

To be able to continue to protect your privacy and to conform to changing generally accepted practices we reserve the right to change this privacy notice. We may need to change our notice to comply with future government regulations which are constantly changing as the internet evolves. 

#### **How To Communicate About Privacy:**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please mail a letter to our corporate office with the following caption. ATT: Privacy Manager  **Elite Cosmos ****International Co. Ltd.**
